Lucas Luz

Full-Stack Web Developer



- Portuguese
- Amsterdam, NL

in Icalazansl

- 🔘 Icalazansi 🔭 Iluz.dev

Skills

HMTL | SCSS | JS
Ruby | Rails | React
SQL | Git Hub | Git
G-Suite | Mac | PS



Professional Experience

Catering Manager @ Google Amsterdam,

Vermaat

Apr 2018 – May 2022 Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Asst. Catering Manager @ Google São Paulo,

Food+ by Compass Feb 2017 – Mar 2018 São Paulo, Brazil

Customer Success Specialist, Practo ☑ 2015 - 2016 São Paulo, Brazil

About Me

You can find my latest projects on my GitHub or website as I keep working to improve myself and my work.

Before I became a developer, I managed international teams and events for the past five years, responsible for a tech giant's internal catering services and external events.

In a "stay-at-home" era, I've produced and also presented virtual cooking/barista classes for a number of tech companies.

≥ Latest Projects

HomeBar App, Ruby | HTML | SCSS | JS ☑

The App is simple to use; Select the **ingredients you have** at home, so the app tells which **cocktails you can make**, or you're **just a few ingredients away**. It's like having a bartender at your fingertip.

- Project owner and lead
- Designed, implemented and tested the algorithm
- Devise and other gem integrations

Freddies Fiets, Ruby | HTML | SCSS | JS ☑

The First Full-Stack project ever(!) is a **marketplace** to rent or lease a bike.

- Vanilla JS for navbar transition and typed JS
- Seeding, Cloudinary and Mapbox API integration
- Full-Stack development

Education

Full-Stack Web Developer | Bootcamp, Le Wagon 🖸

Jul 2022 – Sep 2022 | Amsterdam, The Netherlands

A ten-week Bootcamp that, focuses on **Software Architecture**, Relational **DB - SQL**, OOP, **Ruby** on Rails, **JS**, and invent, pitch, design, code, and **deploy** a project during the two final weeks.

Marketing Management | Certificate, Insper ☑

2015 - 2016 | São Paulo, Brazil

From marketing research and customer behaviour to the breakdown of the marketing mix, as well as integrated communication and value creation through products and services.

Events Management | B. Tech, Anhembi Morumbi University 2012 – 2013 | São Paulo, Brazil

Languages

Portuguese (Native) | English (Fluent) | Dutch (A2) | Spanish



Coffee | Cycling | Pets | Cocktails | Boardgames | Coding